akitio.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy | AKiTiO

AKiTiO is committed to protect our customer's privacy. This statement is meant to inform our users of how we define, gather and utilize personally identifiable information. AKiTiO will take reasonable steps to protect user privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this policy and the applicable laws.

### Information Collected

We collect information as necessary to enable us to identify you and respond to your requests for our products and services, to provide and improve them, and to send you information and support from time to time. When you use these services on our website, you may be asked to submit information such as name, email address, address, phone number, your firmware version, and areas of interest. We may also ask you where you have purchased our products, and for other information that will help us understand more about your needs or help us process your requests for information.

We use all personal information in accordance with this policy. Our information collection and use practices are described in more detail below:

  * **Help Desk Support:** If you use our help desk, you may be asked for personal information such as name and email address as well as product name, firmware version and other information related to your computer and your network environment to help us determine what the technical issues are and how best to help you resolve them.
  * **Product Registration:** Registration information may include personal information such as name and email address and other information related to our products such as model name, serial number and proof of purchase.
  * **Warranty Services:** If you would like to return a product for repair under warranty, you may be asked for personal information such as name, address, phone number and other information related to our products including model name, serial number and proof of purchase. Submitting an RMA application will also require you to have a registered member account in order to submit a ticket on our help desk.
  * **Newsletter:** When you subscribe to receive newsletters from AKiTiO, we will ask you for your email address to enable us to process your request and to send you information regarding our products and services.

#### How do we use this information?

The personal data collected through these services such as name and email address are used solely by AKiTiO for the purpose of communicating personally with you. The additional information you send us is used primarily to answer your questions but this information is also stored in our system for future references, if you contact us again and for our team to troubleshoot and improve our products and services.

#### Can I view and delete this information?

 If you have a registered account, you can login to our website in the Support section and view the data you have previously submitted in the User Menu. To delete your information, some of the data can be deleted using the web interface but some information can only be deleted by our staff members.

  * **Help Desk Ticket:** The tickets can be viewed online after login in the Tickets menu. To delete one or all of your tickets from our system, please submit a new ticket or reply to an existing ticket and let us know which information you would like to have deleted.
  * **Product Registration:** Any products you have registered can be viewed and deleted after login in the User Menu under Product Registration List.
  * **RMA Application:** Any RMA applications you have submitted can be viewed, edited and deleted after login in the User Menu under RMA Submissions.
  * **Newsletter:** To remove your email address from our newsletter list, please click on the "Unsubscribe" link in any of the newsletter messages you have received from us. As an alternative, if you have a registered account on this website, you can login and then unsubscribe from within the User Menu under Newsletter Subscription.
  * **Member Account:** You can edit your profile after login in the User Menu under My Details. To completely delete your account, we will have to also remove all relevant information that you have previously submitted. If you would like to do that, either let us know through our help desk or email us at [privacy@akitio.com](mailto:privacy@akitio.com?subject=Account%20Removal)

### Cookies

Cookies are small bits of text that are downloaded to the devices you use to reach and use a website. Your browser or device holds these cookies and makes them available every time you visit that site again so that it can recognize you and remember important information about you.

#### Can I change my cookie preferences?

You can always change your cookie preferences or delete existing cookies from the controls at the bottom of every page on this website. Browser settings also allow you to choose whether or not to accept cookies or limit certain cookies. Most browsers also provide functionality that lets you review and erase cookies.

#### How do we use cookies?

The types of information typically collected by cookies include information relating to your use of our website, your device’s IP address and browser type and how you arrived on this website. We primarily use cookies to provide user authentication for features like the help desk, product registration and RMA services but we also make use of visitor statistics to improve your user experience.

#### What cookies do we use?

Below is a list of each category of cookies we use and why we use each cookie. First party cookies are our own cookies set by Akitio, controlled by us and used to provide information about the usage of our website.

  * **Essential Cookies:** These cookies are essential to use certain features on our website that require authentication, like the help desk, product registration and RMA services or form submissions like the newsletter subscription and the warranty lookup function. Without these cookies, these features will not function. After you login to our website, these non-persistent cookies will expire if you haven't viewed a page or engaged with our website in 5 hours and you will need to re-authenticate in order to be logged into our site again.
  * **Analytics Cookies:** Analytics cookies allow us to improve our services by collecting information about your use of this website. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. We also gather information about what folks are searching for. We use all this information in order to improve our content, plan site enhancements, and measure overall site effectiveness, and therefore to make the site better and more hopefully fitting to your needs. We can’t identify you personally through the use of these cookies and your IP address is anonymized.
  * **Third Party Cookies:** Some of the cookies on our website are operated by third parties, such as Twitter, YouTube or Facebook. Some of these third parties may use cookies to allow them to deliver the services they are providing. Some of the cookies operated by third parties may be used for analytics purposes, such as to monitor, analyze and prevent fraudulent traffic or other suspicious activities. We do not control these third parties or their use of cookies. This means it is not possible for us to manage these cookies. This policy only covers the use of cookies by AKiTiO and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party. Some of these third party cookies are not session based and have varying expiry dates. Please check the websites of these third parties for details on how they use cookies.

### And Finally

AKiTiO may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law.

AKiTiO may modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time.

If you have any questions about this policy or your data that has been collected, please feel free to email us at [privacy@akitio.com](mailto:privacy@akitio.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

**Last updated: June 9, 2018**
